export default [
  {
    question:
      " A triangle that has 3 equal sides and 3 equal angles is known as ",
    answer: [
      "scalene triangle",
      "isosceles triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    id: 0,
  },

  {
    question: " Area of a triangle with base b and height h is represented by",
    answer: ["1⁄2 × bh", "2 + bh", "2 × bh", "2⁄bh"],
    correct: 0,
    id: 1,
  },

  {
    question: " A triangle with the angle of 90 ° is called ",
    answer: [
      "vertical triangle",
      "supplementary triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
      "reflective triangle",
    ],
    correct: 2,
    id: 2,
  },

  {
    question:
      "A triangle that has 2 equal sides and 2 equal angles is known as ",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "right angle",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    id: 3,
  },

  {
    question:
      " A triangle that has no equal sides and no equal angles is known as ",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    id: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "The obtuse-angled triangle must have ",
    answer: [
      "four obtuse angles",
      "three obtuse angles",
      "two obtuse angles",
      "one obtuse angle",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    id: 5,
  },

  {
    question: "The triangles can be classified on the basis of",
    answer: [
      "the number of equal sides",
      "the types of angles",
      "length of line segments",
      "both a and b",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    id: 6,
  },

  {
    question: "The right-angled triangle must have",
    answer: [
      "four right angles",
      "three right angles",
      "one right angle",
      "two right angles",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    id: 7,
  },

  {
    question:
      " A plane which is formed by three straight edges as its sides is called",
    answer: ["triangle", "quadrilateral", "pentagon", "hexagon"],
    correct: 0,
    id: 8,
  },

  {
    question: "All of the angles in a triangle add up to ___.",
    answer: ["180 degrees", "270 degrees", "90 degrees", "300 degree"],
    correct: 0,
    id: 9,
  },

  {
    question:
      "If perimeter of a triangle is 100cm and the length of two sides are 30cm and 40cm, the length of third side will be",
    answer: ["30cm", "40cm", "50cm", "60cm"],
    correct: 0,
    id: 10,
  },

  {
    question: "The perimeter of an equilateral triangle of side 5cm is: ",
    answer: ["25cm", "15cm", "20cm", "10cm"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 11,
  },

  {
    question:
      " if a triangle has sides of 7cm,5cm,3cm what type of triangle is",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    id: 12,
  },
  {
    question:
      " if a triangle has sides of 7cm,5cm,5cm what type of triangle is",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    id: 13,
  },
  {
    question:
      " if a triangle has sides of 5cm,5cm,5cm what type of triangle is",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    id: 14,
  },
  {
    question:
      " if a triangle has angles of 60deg, 60deg, 60deg what type of triangle is",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    id: 15,
  },
  {
    question:
      " if a triangle has angles of 100deg, 40deg, 40deg what type of triangle is",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    id: 16,
  },
  {
    question:
      " if a triangle has angles of 20deg, 80deg, 80deg what type of triangle is",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    id: 17,
  },
  {
    question:
      " if a triangle has angles of 30deg, 70deg, 80deg what type of triangle is",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    id: 18,
  },
  {
    question: "The perimeter of an equilateral triangle of side 15cm is: ",
    answer: ["25cm", "45cm", "75cm", "10cm"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 19,
  },
  {
    question: "The Area of a triangle with base 8cm height 20cm is: ",
    answer: ["85cm sq", "80cm sq", "75cm sq", "10cm sq"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 20,
  },
  {
    question: "The Area of a triangle with base 8cm height 15cm is: ",
    answer: ["85cm sq", "80cm sq", "75cm sq", "60cm sq"],
    correct: 3,
    id: 21,
  },
  {
    question: "The Area of a triangle with base 4cm height 16cm is: ",
    answer: ["84cm sq", "42cm sq", "44cm sq", "32cm sq"],
    correct: 3,
    id: 22,
  },
  {
    question: "The Area of a triangle with base 80cm height 20cm is: ",
    answer: ["850cm sq", "800cm sq", "750cm sq", "700cm sq"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 23,
  },
  {
    question: "The Area of a triangle with base 17cm height 4cm is: ",
    answer: ["54cm sq", "43cm sq", "34cm sq", "36cm sq"],
    correct: 2,
    id: 24,
  },
  {
    question: "In triangle ABC, if AB=BC and ∠B = 50°, ∠A will be: ",
    answer: ["54deg", "65deg", "74deg", "36deg"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 25,
  },
  {
    question: "In triangle ABC, if AB=BC and ∠B = 70°, ∠A will be: ",
    answer: ["54deg", "65deg", "45deg", "55deg"],
    correct: 3,
    id: 26,
  },
  {
    question: "In triangle ABC, if AB=BC and ∠B = 80°, ∠A will be: ",
    answer: ["54deg", "43deg", "50deg", "36deg"],
    correct: 2,
    id: 27,
  },
  {
    question: "In a right triangle, the longest side is: ",
    answer: ["Perpendicular", " Hypotenuse", "Base", " None of the above"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 28,
  },
];
